app-o-trap.com 2013-01-30

# Privacy Policy

The following privacy policy is licensed under the [Creative Commons](http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-sa/3.0/).

### Website Visitors

Like most website operators, App-o-Trap collects _non-personally-identifying_ information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, your language preference, the referring site, the date and time of each request, and any Javascript errors that occur during your visit. App-o-Trap’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how App-o-Trap’s visitors use its website so we can make improvements and fix bugs. From time to time, App-o-Trap may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

App-o-Trap avoids collecting potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses except to the extent necessary to provide certain services. 

### Aggregated Statistics

App-o-Trap may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. For instance, App-o-Trap may monitor the most popular pages on app-o-trap.com sites. App-o-Trap may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, App-o-Trap does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

### Google App Engine

Some of App-o-Trap's services may be provided by Google App Engine, a service operated by Google (a third party service provider). As such, you should assume that any information you provide to App-o-Trap may be available to App-o-Trap and to Google. For details about the specific privacy guarantees made by Google in its capacity as a service provider, please refer to [code.google.com/appengine/privacy.html](http://code.google.com/appengine/privacy.html).

### Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information

App-o-Trap discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on App-o-Trap’s behalf or to provide services available at App-o-Trap’s websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using App-o-Trap’s websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. App-o-Trap will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, App-o-Trap discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when App-o-Trap believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of App-o-Trap, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of a App-o-Trap website and have supplied your email address, App-o-Trap may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with App-o-Trap and our products. We primarily use our various product blogs to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. App-o-Trap takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

### Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. App-o-Trap uses cookies to help App-o-Trap identify and track visitors, their usage of App-o-Trap website, and their website access preferences. App-o-Trap visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using App-o-Trap’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of App-o-Trap’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

### Javascript Errors

App-o-Trap’s software products are complex. Occasionally, error conditions which we did not anticipate may occur. If such an error condition occurs on your computer, we may log a small amount of non-personally-identifying information about the error in order to help our engineers prevent it from occurring again.

### Business Transfers

If App-o-Trap, or substantially all of its assets were acquired, or in the unlikely event that App-o-Trap goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquiror of App-o-Trap may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.

### Ads

Ads appearing on any of our websites may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. Except in the section "Advertiser Cookies" immediately below, this Privacy Policy discusses the use of cookies by App-o-Trap and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers. For more information about advertiser cookies you should consult the privacy policies of the specific advertising networks you wish to learn more about.

### Advertiser Cookies

Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on your prior visits to the App-o-Trap website. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads based on your visit to the App-o-Trap site and/or other sites on the Internet. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [advertising opt-out page](http://www.google.com/privacy/ads/). 

### Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, App-o-Trap may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in App-o-Trap’s sole discretion. App-o-Trap encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.

Thanks for reading our privacy policy. Don't forget to check out [Automattic](http://automattic.com/), purveyors of only the finest web software. For example, [Wordpress](http://www.wordpress.com/) is a handy free blog service with reasonably-priced upgrades.
